[
    {
        "front": "Atsui",
        "back": "Hot (For Weather)",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Atatakai",
        "back": "Hot (For Object)",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Tsumetai",
        "back": "Cold (For Objects)",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Samui",
        "back": "Cold (For Weather)",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Kibishii",
        "back": "Strict",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Takai",
        "back": "Expensive, Tall",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Yasui",
        "back": "Inexpensive, Cheap",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Muzukashii",
        "back": "Difficult",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Yasashii",
        "back": "Easy, Kind, Gentle",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Omoshiroi",
        "back": "Interesting",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Hayai",
        "back": "Fast, Quick",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Osoi",
        "back": "Slow",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "ii",
        "back": "Good",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Yokunai",
        "back": "Not Good",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Oishii",
        "back": "Tasty",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Sukunai",
        "back": "Little",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Totemo",
        "back": "Very",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Kuni",
        "back": "Country",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Itsumo",
        "back": "Always",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Nihongo",
        "back": "Japanese Language",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Eigo",
        "back": "English",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Ryōri",
        "back": "Dish, food, cuisine",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Kōhii",
        "back": "Coffee",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Atarashii",
        "back": "New",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Furui",
        "back": "Old (things)",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Isogashii",
        "back": "Busy",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Tanoshii",
        "back": "Enjoyable",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Ōkii",
        "back": "Big",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Chiisai",
        "back": "Small",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Hikui",
        "back": "Low",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Warui",
        "back": "Bad ",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Donna",
        "back": "What kind of",
        "chapter": 5
    },
    {
        "front": "Dōmo",
        "back": "Thanks (informal)",
        "chapter": 5
    }
]